Now we go to Jane who is going to tell us about what's happening
in town this weekend.
Right, thanks Andrew,
and now on to what's new,
and do we really need yet another sports shop in Bradcaster?
Well, most of you probably know Sports World - the branch of a Danish
sports goods company that opened a few years ago-
it's attracted a lot of custom,
and so the company has now decided to open another branch in the area.
It's going to be in the shopping centre to the west of Bradcaster,
so that will be good news for all of you who've found the original
shop in the north of the town hard to get to.
I was invited to a special preview and I can promise you, this is
the ultimate in sports retailing.
The whole place has been given a new minimalist look with the company's signature colours of black
and red.
The first three floors have a huge range of sports clothing as well as
equipment,
and on the top floor there's a cafe and a book and DVD section.
You'll find all the well-known names as well as some less well-known ones.
If they haven't got exactly what you want in stock they promise to get
it for you in ten days.
Unlike the other store, where it can take up to fourteen days.
They cover all the major sports, including football, tennis and swimming,
but they particularly focus on running,
and they claim to have the widest range of equipment in the country.
As well as that, a whole section of the third floor is devoted to
sports bags, including the latest designs from the States - if you can't find
what you want here, it doesn't exist!
The shop will be open from 9.00 am this Saturday
and if you go along to the opening then you'll have the chance to
meet the national 400 metres running champion Paul King,
who's coming along to open the shop,
and he will be staying around until about midday to chat to any fans who want to meet him
and sign autographs.
Then there will be a whole range of special attractios all weekend.
There will be free tickets for local sporting events for the first 50 customers,
and also a special competition open to all.
Just answer fifteen out of twenty sports questions correctly to win a signed copy
of Paul King's DVD 'Spring Tips',
while the first person to get all the questions correct gets a year's free
membership of the Bradcaster Gym.
All entrants will receive a special Sports calendar with details of all Bradcaster fixtures
in the coming year.
One of the special opening offers is a fitness test-a complete review of your cardiac fitness
and muscle tone, actually done in the shop by qualified staff.
This would normally cost 30.00 but is available at half price for this month
only.
There are only a limited number of places available for this,
so to make a booking phone 560341.
In addition, if you open an account you get lots more special offers including
the chance to try out equipment at special open evenings….